const questions = [
  {
    question:
      'How many times is Jon stabbed when he is murdered at Castle Black?',
    choices: ['1', '6', '9', '10'],
    answer: '6'
  },
  {
    question: 'What name do the wildlings call Jon Snow?',
    choices: ['Jon', 'Big Boi', 'Puny', 'King Crow'],
    answer: 'King Crow'
  },
  {
    question: 'What does Sansa place in the hand of Lyanna Stark’s statue?',
    choices: ['A feather', 'A necklace', 'An earring', 'Snow'],
    answer: 'A feather'
  },
  {
    question:
      "What's the name of the explosive that gave the Lannisters the edge in the Battle of Blackwater?",
    choices: ['Dragonfire', 'Godsfire', 'Wildfire', 'Wildseed'],
    answer: 'Wildfire'
  },
  {
    question:
      'Who said, "Go drink until it feels like you did the right thing"?',
    choices: ['Jamie Lannister', 'Tyrion Lannister', 'Bronn', 'Varys'],
    answer: 'Bronn'
  },
  {
    question:
      'What does Daenerys mean when she says "Shekh ma shieraki anni" to Khal Drogo?',
    choices: [
      'Sound did silence me',
      'Moon of my life',
      'My sun and stars',
      'I am yours and you are mine'
    ],
    answer: 'My sun and stars'
  },
  {
    question: 'How is Ser Davos colloquially known as?',
    choices: [
      'The Sea Knight',
      'Davos the Smuggler',
      'The Cabbage Duke',
      'The Onion Knight'
    ],
    answer: 'The Onion Knight'
  },
  {
    question: 'Who masterminded the plot to kill King Joffrey?',
    choices: ['Littlefinger', 'Olenna Tyrell', 'Margaery Tyrell', 'Arya Stark'],
    answer: 'Littlefinger'
  },
  {
    question: 'What is the official Lannister family motto?',
    choices: [
      'Hear me roar',
      'A Lannister always pays his debts',
      'None so fierce',
      'Never knowingly undersold'
    ],
    answer: 'Hear Me Roar'
  },
  {
    question:
      'What name does Littlefinger use to disguise Sansa when he brings her to the Eyrie?',
    choices: ['Susan', 'Alayne', 'Margarette', 'Elena'],
    answer: 'Alayne'
  },
  {
    question: 'What are Rickon’s last words to Bran?',
    choices: [
      'Look after Hodor',
      "I don't want to leave you",
      'When will I see you again?',
      'Winter is coming'
    ],
    answer: "I don't want to leave you"
  },
  {
    question:
      'According to Jon, how many times has a King Beyond the Wall attacked the Seven Kingdoms?',
    choices: ['6', '0', '2', '10'],
    answer: '6'
  },
  {
    question:
      '"When you play the Game of Thrones, you win or you die." Cersei Lannister first uttered these words to who?',
    choices: ['Varys', 'Ned Stark', 'Robert Baratheon', 'Margaery Tyrell'],
    answer: 'Ned Stark'
  },
  {
    question:
      'Who helped Daenerys and her followers get into the city of Qarth?',
    choices: [
      'The Spice King',
      "She didn't get in",
      'Jorah Mormont',
      'Xaro Xhoan Daxos'
    ],
    answer: 'Xaro Xhoan Daxos'
  },
  {
    question:
      'Where did Tywin and the Lannister army set up camp during the Ware of the Five Kings?',
    choices: ['Casterly Rock', 'Riverrun', 'The Twins', 'Harrenhal'],
    answer: 'Harrenhal'
  },
  {
    question: 'How was Renly Baratheon killed?',
    choices: ['Stabbed by a shadow', 'In his sleep', 'Poisoned', 'In battle'],
    answer: 'Stabbed by a shadow'
  },
  {
    question: 'Samwell of house...?',
    choices: ['Tully', 'Greyjoy', 'Tarly', 'Frey'],
    answer: 'Tarly'
  },
  {
    question: 'Barristan Selmy is slain by',
    choices: ['Sons of the Harpy', 'The Kings Guard', 'A slave', 'City Watch'],
    answer: 'Sons of the Harpy'
  },
  {
    question: 'Myrcella Baratheon is killed by who?',
    choices: ['Ellaria Sand', 'Obara Sand', 'Tyene Sand', 'Nymeria Sand'],
    answer: 'Ellaria Sand'
  },
  {
    question:
      'What was the name of the first Targaryen king who conquered Westeros with his two sisters?',
    choices: [
      'Aegon II Targaryen',
      'Aegon IV Targaryen',
      'Aegon I Targaryen',
      'Rhaegar Targaryen'
    ],
    answer: 'Aegon I Targaryen'
  },
  {
    question: 'What do the wildings call themselves?',
    choices: ['Folk of the north', 'Travellers', 'Free Folk', 'Crows'],
    answer: 'Free Folk'
  },
  {
    question: 'What did Rickon Stark name his direwolf?',
    choices: ['Summer', 'Grey Wind', 'Nymeria', 'Shaggydog'],
    answer: 'Shaggydog'
  }
];

export default questions;
